<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on DavidCraddock.Games</title>
    <link>https://davidcraddock.games/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on DavidCraddock.Games</description>
    <image>
      <title>DavidCraddock.Games</title>
      <url>https://davidcraddock.games/mugshot.png</url>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/mugshot.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.131.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>David Paul Craddock</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:40:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidcraddock.games/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1 player Time Crisis 2 with Sinden Light Gun on PCSX2</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/time-crisis-2-1-player-sinden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddock.games/time-crisis-2-1-player-sinden/</guid>
      <description>I have built a good setup for single player Time Crisis 2 on the PC, using a PS2 emulator. It is only single player at the moment, I&amp;rsquo;m still working on the best way to enable two player.
Software Time Crisis 2 (USA version) for PS2 - SLUS-210219 Sinden Light Gun Utility Patched with Recoil support for Patched PS2 Emulator Sinden Light Gun Utility PCSX2 Emulator patched for Recoil PCSX2 Emulator Time Crisis 2 Target Cursors Cursor pack Time Crisis 2 HD Retexture Pack (Paetron-supported) https://gbatemp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epoch Light Gun Game Review</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/epoch-light-gun-game-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 16:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddock.games/epoch-light-gun-game-review/</guid>
      <description>I setup and played the &amp;lsquo;Epoch&amp;rsquo; rail-shooter game available on steam, with my Sinden light gun setup.
Negatives I have to say, I didn&amp;rsquo;t like the mechanics of the game. The gameplay seemed pretty boring, and instead of one-shot-one-kill, you have to constantly &amp;lsquo;wear down&amp;rsquo; enemies through shooting at them, and moving out of their way.
This doesn&amp;rsquo;t really work very well on the Sinden light gun, as, although there are controls for moving - 4 buttons and a d-pad - on the gun, constantly having to switch to them and away from the &amp;lsquo;aim and fire&amp;rsquo; action does not work very well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batsugun</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/batsugun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddock.games/batsugun/</guid>
      <description>I played through the version of [https://store.steampowered.com/app/2023000/Batsugun/](Batsugun on Steam) on the arcade setup.
It is part of the [Toaplan Arcade Shoot ‘Em Up Collection Vol.4](Toaplan Arcade Shoot &amp;lsquo;Em Up Collection Vol.4).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunstar Heroes Review</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/gunstar-heroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddock.games/gunstar-heroes/</guid>
      <description>For years I have been stuck with a working megadrive with a Gunstar Heroes cartridge that works UP UNTIL A POINT, and then crashes.
If it were fully working, this Gunstar Heroes megadrive cartridge would be worth £250 at least at Ebay current prices!
But more annoyingly, I have not been able to play the game properly.
When Sega decided to discontinue the Sega Megadrive Collection on Steam, they offered a low price to buy all of the games, one of which was - you guessed it, Gunstar Heroes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Gaming Blog</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/new-gaming-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddock.games/new-gaming-blog/</guid>
      <description>This is my new gaming blog, where I will write reviews of games I&amp;rsquo;ve played, game accessories I&amp;rsquo;ve bought, and anything else PC or console gaming-related that I can think of.
It is using the same setup as my main https://davidcraddock.net blog - as in - it&amp;rsquo;s self-hosted, and uses the Hugo Go-based static blogging engine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Crisis 2 Setup</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/time-crisis-2-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddock.games/time-crisis-2-setup/</guid>
      <description>Time Crisis 2 is a light-gun shooter arcade game developed and published by Namco. It was released in arcades in 1997, and later ported to the PlayStation 2 in 2001. It is the second instalment in the Time Crisis series.
The game features a two-player mode, where each player takes turns using a light gun to shoot enemies and reload. Players can duck behind cover to avoid enemy fire, and pop out to shoot enemies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget Home Retro Arcade Setup</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/arcade-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddock.games/arcade-setup/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted an arcade machine in my home. But I could never really afford one, in terms of time and space. Recently I thought to myself, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not getting any younger&amp;rdquo;. So I built an arcade setup mostly just using the things I already had in the home.
Games The ROMs I have are all stored on my file server upstairs. I can get around a 3gbits/sec connection via my 10gbits/sec home network, so there is no performance &amp;lsquo;hit&amp;rsquo; in streaming them off the network drive - it has similar speed and latency to a physical drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Age: Veilguard - First Impressions</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/dragon-age-veilguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddock.games/dragon-age-veilguard/</guid>
      <description>I pre-ordered Dragon Age: Veilguard, and started playing it as soon as it downloaded after release.
First impressions? Quite positive! Some initial thoughts:
I&amp;rsquo;ve been a long-time BioWare fan since Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate, but was massively disappointed with Mass Effect: Andromeda, so much so that I didn&amp;rsquo;t even bother playing Anthem. I do like the setting and the characterisations in the Dragon Age series, and thought it was worth pre-ordering this game just in case they didn&amp;rsquo;t totally mess it up.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
